<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE reference
  PUBLIC "-//IBM//DTD DITA IBM Reference//EN" "ibm-reference.dtd">
<reference xml:lang="en-us" id="countingwordsinsegmentswithfuzzymatches">
  <title>Counting words in segments with fuzzy matches</title>
  <prolog>
    <metadata>
      <keywords><!--Insert <indexterm> tags here--></keywords>
    </metadata>
  </prolog>
  <refbody>
    <section/>
    <section>
      <title/>
      <indexterm>counting<indexterm>matches</indexterm></indexterm>
      <indexterm>document<indexterm>Counting words in segments with fuzzy
        matches</indexterm></indexterm>
      <p><keyword conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/tm4w"/> provides a facility for
        counting words in segments with fuzzy matches. The result is shown in a window and can be
        saved in a file. The words in segments with fuzzy matches are grouped in classes. The column
        Class-0 lists the number of words in segments with fuzzy matches which are only different in
        white space or inline tagging. The column Class-1 lists the number of words in segments with
        one different word , class-2 with two different words and so on. To count the number of
        words in all the documents of a folder, see <xref href="countnumber.dita#countnumber"/></p>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Prerequisites</title>
      <p>At least one document must exist in the selected folder and the document has to be
        analyzed.</p>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Calling sequence</title>
      <p>Select: <ol>
          <li>At least one document from the <q>Document List</q> window</li>
          <li>from the menu</li>
        </ol></p>
      <p>The <q>Count Words</q> window (see <xref href="countmatch.dita#countmatch/matchcnt"/>) is
        displayed. <required-cleanup><indexterm>windows<indexterm>Count
            Words</indexterm></indexterm></required-cleanup><fig id="matchcnt" expanse="column">
          <title>Count Words window</title><image placement="break" href="fuzzycount.gif"
              ><alt>Figure shows Count Words window</alt></image></fig>
      </p>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Options and parameters</title>
      <parml>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Documents</pt>
          <pd>This box contains the list of the documents you selected in the <q>Document List</q>
            window.</pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Options</pt>
          <pd>Select: <parml>
              <plentry><pt>Fuzzy matches by class </pt>
                <pd>To count the number of words in segments with fuzzy matches in the selected
                  documents. </pd></plentry>
              <plentry><pt>Output to </pt>
                <pd>In this block you define where you want the system to save the results:
                </pd></plentry>
              <plentry><pt>Screen</pt>
                <pd>he result of the word count is displayed on your screen. This option is selected
                  automatically. </pd></plentry>
              <plentry><pt>File </pt>
                <pd>Select this option to also store the count results in a file. <p>You can:
                  </p></pd></plentry>
            </parml></pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Output to</pt>
          <pd>In this block you define where you want the system to save the results: <parml>
              <plentry><pt>Screen</pt>
                <pd>The result of the word count is displayed on your screen. This option is
                  selected automatically.</pd></plentry>
              <plentry><pt>File</pt>
                <pd>Select this option to also store the count results in a file. You can: <ul>
                    <li>Accept the proposed file name.</li>
                    <li>Type a file name of your choice.</li>
                    <li>Click <b>Select…</b> to display the <q>Select File</q> window from where you
                      can choose the file name without having to type it (for a detailed
                      description, see <xref href="selfile.dita#selfile"/>).</li>
                    <li>Select the format of the count result file. The supported formats are <ul>
                        <li>ASCII (plain text)</li>
                        <li>HTML</li>
                        <li>XML </li>
                      </ul></li>
                  </ul></pd></plentry>
            </parml></pd>
        </plentry>
      </parml>
      <p>Click <b>Count</b> to begin counting words</p>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Results</title>
      <p>The results of the word count are shown, for example, in the <q>Word Count Results – Fuzzy
          Matches per Class</q> window (see <xref href="countmatch.dita#countmatch/wctmm"/>).
              <required-cleanup><indexterm>windows<indexterm>Word Count Results – Fuzzy Matches per
              Class</indexterm></indexterm></required-cleanup><fig id="wctmm" expanse="column">
          <title>Word Count Results – Fuzzy Matches per Class window</title><image placement="break"
            href="fuzzycountresult.gif"><alt>Figure shows Word Count Results – Fuzzy Matches per
              Class window</alt></image></fig></p>
      <p>The window contains the following columns: <dl>
          <dlentry><dt>Documents</dt>
            <dd>The name of the documents.</dd></dlentry>
          <dlentry><dt>Total</dt>
            <dd>The number of words in the documents.</dd></dlentry>
          <dlentry><dt>Class-zero</dt>
            <dd>The number of words in segments with fuzzy matches where no source words are
              different.</dd></dlentry>
          <dlentry><dt>Class-1</dt>
            <dd>The number of words in segments with fuzzy matches where one source word is
              different.</dd></dlentry>
          <dlentry><dt>Class-2</dt>
            <dd>The number of words in segments with fuzzy matches where two source words are
              different.</dd></dlentry>
          <dlentry><dt>Class-3</dt>
            <dd>The number of words in segments with fuzzy matches where three source words are
              different.</dd></dlentry>
          <dlentry><dt>Class-4</dt>
            <dd>The number of words in segments with fuzzy matches where four source words are
              different.</dd></dlentry>
          <dlentry><dt>Class-5</dt>
            <dd>he number of words in segments with fuzzy matches where five source words are
              different.</dd></dlentry>
          <dlentry><dt>Class-6up</dt>
            <dd>The number of words in segments with fuzzy matches where six or more source words
              are different.</dd></dlentry>
        </dl></p>
      <p>If you selected the output option, the results are stored in the same format in the
        specified file.</p>
      <p>To return to the previous window, close the respective <q>Word Count Result – Fuzzy Matches
          per Class</q> window.</p>
    </section>
  </refbody>
</reference>
