<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE reference PUBLIC "-//IBM//DTD DITA IBM Reference//EN" "ibm-reference.dtd">
<reference xml:lang="en-us" id="doc_SearchFuzzy">
  <title>Search segments with fuzzy matches</title>
  <prolog>
    <metadata>
      <keywords><!--Insert <indexterm> tags here--></keywords>
    </metadata>
  </prolog>
  <refbody>
    <section>
      <title/>
      <p><keyword conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/tm4w"/> provides a function called
          <q>Search Segments with Fuzzy Matches</q>, which works across all or some documents of a
          folder or a group of folders.</p>
      <p>This function is helpful in e.g. the pre-translation process to identify segments which can
         be easily translated by using a fuzzy memory proposal and change some tagging or a few words.</p>
      <p>Note that <keyword conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/tm4w"/> searches and replaces
         only pieces of text that can be translated. Markup tags cannot be changed. Users can control
         whether <keyword conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/tm4w"/> searches in protected
         text areas, like inline tags, for translatable text. This is helpful if users want to
         include markup tag attribute values in the search process.</p>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Prerequisites</title>
      <p>The <keyword conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/tm4w"/>-folder must exist, and its
         documents must have been analyzed.</p>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Calling sequence</title>
      <p>Start this function from a <q>Folder List</q> window or from a <q>Document List</q> window.
         In this description, the start from the <q>Document List</q>window is described.</p>
      <p><b><u>Select</u></b>: 
        <ol>
          <li>One or more documents you want to have searched through from the <q>Document List</q> window</li>
          <li><b>Fuzzy Segment Search...</b> from the menu</li>
        </ol>
      </p>
      <p>The <q>Search Segments With Fuzzy matches</q> window is displayed. 
        <fig id="fuzzySearch" expanse="column">
          <title>Search Segments With Fuzzy matches window</title>
          <image placement="break" href="doc_SearchFuzzy.gif">
            <alt>Figure shows Search Segments With Fuzzy matches window</alt>
          </image>
        </fig>
      </p>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Options and parameters</title>
      <parml>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Search fuzzy matches </pt>
          <pd>Select in which <q>range of classes</q> should be searched. 
            <ul>
              <li><q>With selected class or higher</q>: searches starting with the selected class and ending at the highest class.</li>
              <li><q>Having the selected class only</q>: searches only in the selected class.</li>
              <li><q>Up to and including the selected class</q>: searches starting from the lowest class up to the selected class.</li>
            </ul>
          </pd>
        </plentry>

        <plentry>
          <pt>Fuzzy search class </pt>
          <pd>Select the class of the segments with fuzzy matches being searched. <p>The <q>class</q> is
              the number of different words between the segment and the memory proposal.</p>
            <p>Differences in white spaces and inline tagging are ignored.</p>
          </pd>
        </plentry>

        <plentry>
          <pt>Show and export differences in search results </pt>
          <pd>Show or hide the differences in the search result. 
            <ul>
              <li>If selected: the differences in the segments are highligted.</li>
              <li>If not selected: the differences in the segments are not highligted.</li>
            </ul>
            <p>This selection works for both, the <b>display</b> function in the section <q>Search
               results</q>, as well as when the search results are <b>exported</b> into an XML file.</p>
          </pd>
        </plentry>

        <plentry>
          <pt>Documents being searched </pt>
          <pd>In this area all searched documents are displayed.</pd>
        </plentry>

        <plentry>
          <pt>Search results </pt>
          <pd>In this area the <b>results</b> of the search process are displayed. <p>For each entry, the folder
              name, the class name, the word count, the document name, the segment number, the
              source-segment data and the source of the memory proposal is shown.</p>
            <p>The <b>differences</b> between the source-text in the segment to be translated, and the source-text 
               of the memory proposal are highlighted in case the option <q>Show and export differences in search 
               results</q> is activated.</p>
          </pd>
        </plentry>

        <plentry>
          <pt>Start search </pt>
          <pd>Starts the search for segments with fuzzy matches. <p>The segments matching the
              selected class are displayed in the result area.</p>
          </pd>
        </plentry>

        <plentry>
          <pt>Stop search </pt>
          <pd>Stops the current search process. </pd>
        </plentry>

        <plentry>
          <pt>Open document </pt>
          <pd>Opens the document, which contains the selected segment, in the translation editor, and makes the segment the active one. 
            <p>You can also open the document and position to the segment by <b>double-clicking</b> the entry in the result list. </p>
          </pd>
        </plentry>

        <plentry>
          <pt>Export results </pt>
          <pd>Exports the found segments as shown in section <q>Search results</q> into an XML-document. In case of
            having selected <q>Show and export differences in search results</q>, the exported
            document contains the differences in tags. &lt;hp1&gt;... &lt;/hp1&gt; indicates <b>inserted</b> text, and
            &lt;hp2&gt;... &lt;/hp2&gt; indicates <b>changed</b> text. 
          </pd>
        </plentry>

        <plentry>
          <pt>Set colors</pt>
          <pd>Opens the "Set Fuzzy Segment Search Colors" dialog, which allows customization of the colors being used in the <b>Search results</b> list.</pd>
        </plentry>

        <plentry>
          <pt>Set font</pt>
          <pd>Opens the "Font" dialog, which allows customization of the font being used in the <b>Search results</b> list.</pd>
        </plentry>

        <plentry>
          <pt>Cancel </pt>
          <pd>Stops the search and the interaction with this window and returns you to the starting
            point.</pd>
        </plentry>

        <plentry>
          <pt>Help </pt>
          <pd>Help Gives information to help you interact with this window.</pd>
        </plentry>
      </parml>
    </section>

    <section>
      <title>Results</title>
      <p>The segments matching the selected class are displayed in the result area.</p>
      <p>Results displayed in the Search Segments With Fuzzy matches window. 
        <fig id="fuzzySearchResult" expanse="column">
          <title>Search Segments With Fuzzy matches window</title>
          <image placement="break" href="changes_131_FuzzySearch.gif">
            <alt>Search Segments With Fuzzy matches window</alt>
          </image>
        </fig>
      </p>
    </section>
  </refbody>
</reference>
