<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE reference PUBLIC "-//IBM//DTD DITA IBM Reference//EN" "ibm-reference.dtd">
<reference xml:lang="en-us" id="eqfr5mst-00209">
  <title>Importing a folder</title>
  <prolog>
    <metadata>
      <keywords><!--Insert <indexterm> tags here--></keywords>
    </metadata>
  </prolog>
  <refbody>
    <section/>
    <section>
      <title/>
      <indexterm>importing<indexterm>folders</indexterm></indexterm>
      <indexterm>folder<indexterm>importing</indexterm></indexterm>
      <p>When translations are prepared centrally before being distributed to individual
        translators, you are strongly recommended to use folders as the means of distributing this
        material, because all related translation material (documents, dictionaries, and <keyword
          conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/xlmems"/>) can be included in one folder.</p>
      <p>Before you can start to work with material that has been exported, you must import the
        material in <keyword conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/tm4w"/>.</p>
      <p>A folder exported to a diskette drive can span more than one diskette. The system prompts
        you to insert the diskettes into the diskette drive in the same sequence they were used
        during export.</p>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Prerequisites</title>
      <p>Ensure that there is sufficient free disk space on your system.</p>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Calling sequence</title>
      <p>Select: <ol>
          <li>The <q>Folder List</q> window from the main window</li>
          <li><b>Import…</b> from the <b>File</b> menu</li>
        </ol></p>
      <p>The <q>Import Folder</q> window (see <xref href="#eqfr5mst-00209/importfolderwin"/>) is
        displayed. <required-cleanup><indexterm>windows<indexterm>Import
          Folder</indexterm></indexterm></required-cleanup><fig id="importfolderwin" expanse="column">
          <title>Import Folder window</title><image placement="break" href="folimp.gif"><alt>Figure
              shows Import Folder window</alt></image></fig>
      </p>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Options and parameters</title>
      <p>You can import a folder from any drive that is defined to your installation.</p>
      <p>On the <q>General</q> page:</p>
      <parml>
        <plentry>
          <pt>From</pt>
          <pd>Select: <ul>
              <li>The drive where the folder to be imported resides.</li>
              <li>The folder from the <b>Folder</b> box. When you have selected a drive, this box
                shows the importable folders on this drive.</li>
            </ul></pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Options</pt>
          <pd>Select: <parml>
              <plentry><pt>With dictionaries</pt>
                <pd>if you wish to import all dictionaries that were previously exported together
                  with the folder. If there are no dictionaries in the folder, this option cannot be
                  selected.</pd></plentry>
              <plentry><pt>With <keyword conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/xlmem"/>
                  databases</pt>
                <pd>if you wish to import all <keyword
                    conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/xlmems"/> that were previously
                  exported with the folder. If there are no <keyword
                    conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/xlmems"/> in the folder, this option
                  cannot be selected.</pd></plentry>
              <plentry><pt>Import folder as</pt>
                <pd>if you wish to import the folder under a different name.</pd></plentry>
            </parml></pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>To</pt>
          <pd>Contains the drive on which <keyword
              conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/tm4w"/> resides. If you have several
              <keyword conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/tm4w"/> installations, select the
            appropriate drive.</pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Import from</pt>
          <pd>Select <q><keyword conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/tm4w"/> folder (FXP)</q>
            for the import of <keyword conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/tm4w"/> folders.
          </pd>
        </plentry>
      </parml>
      <p>The <q>Details</q> page contains information about the selected folder; it
        cannot be changed on this window.</p>
      <parml>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Name</pt>
          <pd>The name of the folder.</pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Description</pt>
          <pd>Additional information about the folder.</pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Date of export</pt>
          <pd>The date and time when the folder was exported.</pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>
            <keyword conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/xlmem"/>
          </pt>
          <pd>The name of the <keyword conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/xlmem"/>
            referenced in this folder.</pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Markup</pt>
          <pd>The name of the markup table used.</pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Export options</pt>
          <pd>This field can contain <b>Selected documents only</b> if the folder was exported with
            this option, otherwise this field is empty.</pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Documents</pt>
          <pd>If the folder contains documents, their file names are displayed here.</pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>
            <keyword conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/xlmems"/>
          </pt>
          <pd>If the folder contains <keyword conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/xlmems"/>,
            their names are displayed here.</pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Dictionaries</pt>
          <pd>If the folder contains dictionaries, their names are displayed here.</pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Note</pt>
          <pd>If the folder contains a note, it is displayed here.</pd>
        </plentry>
      </parml>
      <p>To print a copy of the details, click <b>Print</b>.</p>
      <p>To begin importing the folder, click <b>Import</b>.</p>
      <p>If you import the folder from a diskette drive and the exported folder was written to more
        than one diskette, you are prompted to insert the diskettes in the sequence in which they
        were inserted during export. </p>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Results</title>
      <p>The folder is imported. It is added in the <q>Folder List</q> window, and you can start
        using its contents or the imported dictionaries for document analysis.</p>
      <p>If the folder contains a dictionary with the same name as an existing one, you
        are asked whether the dictionary is to be ignored, or to be imported and automatically
        merged with the existing one.</p>
      <p>If the folder contains a <keyword
          conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/xlmem"/> with the same name as an existing one,
        you are asked whether the <keyword conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/xlmem"/> is to
        be ignored, or to be imported and automatically merged with the existing one.</p>
      <p>An imported folder also contains the markup tables of the folder and document properties.
        During import, markup tables in your system are overwritten if they have the same name and
        the markup table in the folder is a more recent one.</p>
      <p>If you import a folder that already exists but the content of one or more of its
        documents differs from the existing ones, the <q>Set Document Processing Options</q> window
        is displayed. You can then decide for each document whether it is to be imported.</p>
      <p>When you open the imported folder, the <q>Document List</q> window displays the details
        arrangement defined by the sender.</p>
    </section>
  </refbody>
</reference>
