<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE reference
  PUBLIC "-//IBM//DTD DITA IBM Reference//EN" "ibm-reference.dtd">
<reference xml:lang="en-us" id="searchsegmentswithfuzzymatches">
  <title><!--rev=ws03012010-->Search segments with fuzzy matches</title>
  <prolog>
    <metadata>
      <keywords><!--Insert <indexterm> tags here--></keywords>
    </metadata>
  </prolog>
  <refbody>
    <section/>
    <section>
      <title/>
      <p><keyword conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/tm4w"/> provides a Search Segments with
        Fuzzy Matches function, which works across all or some documents of a folder or across a
        group of folders.</p>
      <p>This function might be helpful in the pre-translation process to identify segments which
        can be easily translated by using a fuzzy memory proposal and change some tagging or a few
        words.</p>
      <p>Note that <keyword conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/tm4w"/> searches and replaces
        only pieces of text that can be translated. Markup tags cannot be changed. You can control
        whether <keyword conref="common-symbols.dita#common-symbols/tm4w"/> searches in protected
        text areas, like inline tags, for translatable text. This is helpful if you want to include
        markup tag attribute values in the search process.</p>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Prerequisites</title>
      <p>The folder must exist, and its documents must have been analyzed.</p>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Calling sequence</title>
      <p>You can start this function from a <q>Folder List</q> window or from a <q>Document List</q>
        window. Here the start from the <q>Document List</q>window is described.</p>
      <p>Select: <ol>
          <li>One or more documents you want to have searched through from the <q>Document List</q>
            window</li>
          <li>from the menu</li>
        </ol></p>
      <p>The <q>Search Segments With Fuzzy matches</q> window is displayed (see <xref
          href="#searchsegmentswithfuzzymatches"/>).
              <required-cleanup><indexterm>windows<indexterm>Search Segments With Fuzzy
              matches</indexterm></indexterm></required-cleanup><fig id="fuzzysearch" expanse="column">
          <title>Search Segments With Fuzzy matches window</title><image placement="break"
            href="fuzzysearch.gif"><alt>Figure shows Search Segments With Fuzzy matches
            window</alt></image></fig>
      </p>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Options and parameters</title>
      <parml>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Search fuzzy matches up to </pt>
          <pd>select here the class of the segments with fuzzy matches being searched. <p>The class
              is the number of different words between the segment and the memory proposal.</p>
            <p>Differences in white spaces and inline tagging are ignored.</p></pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Search results </pt>
          <pd>In this area the results of the search are displayed. <p>For each entry the folder
              name, the document name, the segment number, the segment data and the source of the
              memory proposal is shown. </p>
            <p>The differences between the segment text and the memory proposal are
            highlighted.</p></pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Start search </pt>
          <pd>Starts the search for segments with fuzzy matches. <p>The segments which match the
              selected class are displayed in the result area.</p></pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Stop search </pt>
          <pd>Stops the current search. </pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Open document </pt>
          <pd>Opens the document which contains the selected segment and makes the segment the
            active one. Opens the document which contains the selected segment and makes the segment
            the active one. <p>You can also open the document and position to the segment by
              double-clicking the entry in the result list. </p></pd>
        </plentry>
        <plentry>
          <pt>Cancel </pt>
          <pd>Stops the search and the interaction with this window and returns you to the starting
            point. <p>Help Gives information to help you interact with this window. </p></pd>
        </plentry>
      </parml>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Results</title>
      <p>The segments matching the selected class are displayed in the result area.</p>
      <p>Results displayed in the Search Segments With Fuzzy matches window (see <xref
          href="#searchsegmentswithfuzzymatches"/>).
              <required-cleanup><indexterm>windows<indexterm>Search Segments With Fuzzy matches
                window</indexterm></indexterm></required-cleanup><fig id="fuzzysearchresult" expanse="column">
          <title>Search Segments With Fuzzy matches window</title><image placement="break"
            href="fuzzysearchresult.gif"><alt>Search Segments With Fuzzy matches
            window</alt></image></fig>
      </p>
    </section>
  </refbody>
</reference>
